<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Mod settings -->
  <PSC_SettingsCategory>Precision Stockpile Control</PSC_SettingsCategory>
  <!-- Side-tab nav labels -->
  <PSC_SettingsTabWelcome>Welcome</PSC_SettingsTabWelcome>
  <PSC_SettingsTabGeneral>General options</PSC_SettingsTabGeneral>
  <PSC_SettingsTabUI>UI</PSC_SettingsTabUI>
  <PSC_SettingsIntro>Opt-in stockpile tools. A stockpile you never touch behaves exactly like vanilla.</PSC_SettingsIntro>
  <PSC_SettingsQuickStart>Quick start: select a stockpile or shelf, then click Stockpile Control on its Storage tab.</PSC_SettingsQuickStart>
  <!-- Welcome tab: capability list (feature: what it does (where to find it)) -->
  <PSC_WelcomeFeaturesHeader>What you can do</PSC_WelcomeFeaturesHeader>
  <PSC_WelcomeFeatures>• Limits &amp; refill: cap an item's count, or refill only when low (Stockpile Control window, or an item row's marker)\n• Batch hauling: make pawns carry a minimum load per trip (window, or the toggle strip by the button)\n• Feeder routes: push/pull items between storages, source → destination (gizmos on a selected storage)\n• Storage modes: Normal, Frozen, Fill only, or Drain only (gizmo on a selected storage)\n• Fine priority: an a-z tiebreaker by the vanilla Priority button; optional 1-10 levels (turn on in General options)\n• Stockpile alarm: alert when a storage gets too full or too empty (gizmo on a selected storage)\n• On-map overlay: show priorities and all routes on the map (toggle in the bottom-right play settings)\n• Scoped paste: right-click the vanilla Paste button to paste only items, limits, or routes</PSC_WelcomeFeatures>
  <PSC_WelcomeMore>More options in the General options and UI tabs.</PSC_WelcomeMore>
  <PSC_SettingsFeederHeader>Storage routes</PSC_SettingsFeederHeader>
  <PSC_SettingsDefaultOnlyFromSource>New destinations start "Pull only from sources"</PSC_SettingsDefaultOnlyFromSource>
  <PSC_SettingsDefaultOnlyFromSourceTip>When you first set a source for a storage, automatically turn on "Pull only from sources" for it. You can still toggle it per storage.</PSC_SettingsDefaultOnlyFromSourceTip>
  <PSC_SettingsDefaultOnlyToDestinations>New sources start "Push only to destinations"</PSC_SettingsDefaultOnlyToDestinations>
  <PSC_SettingsDefaultOnlyToDestinationsTip>When you first set a destination for a storage, automatically turn on "Push only to destinations" for it. You can still toggle it per storage.</PSC_SettingsDefaultOnlyToDestinationsTip>
  <PSC_SettingsAutoPrioritySource>Auto-lower source priority on new route</PSC_SettingsAutoPrioritySource>
  <PSC_SettingsAutoPrioritySourceTip>When you set a source, automatically nudge its letter one step below the destination so the route works right away (a destination must outrank its source). Stops at "z" and warns you when it can't place — set that by hand. Off by default.</PSC_SettingsAutoPrioritySourceTip>
  <PSC_SettingsAutoPriorityDestination>Auto-raise destination priority on new route</PSC_SettingsAutoPriorityDestination>
  <PSC_SettingsAutoPriorityDestinationTip>When you set a destination, automatically nudge its letter one step above the source so the route works right away (a destination must outrank its source). Stops at no letter and warns you when it can't place — set that by hand. Off by default.</PSC_SettingsAutoPriorityDestinationTip>
  <PSC_SettingsSkipHops>Deliver straight to the end of a route chain</PSC_SettingsSkipHops>
  <PSC_SettingsSkipHopsTip>When on, an item that would relay through a multi-step route (A to B to C) is carried straight to the furthest storage in the chain that can accept it, instead of being dropped and picked up again at each step. If the end is full, it falls back to the nearest step that has room. Note: a middle storage you use as a buffer (with its own limit) gets flown past and won't fill while this is on. Off by default.</PSC_SettingsSkipHopsTip>
  <PSC_SettingsSkipLooseItems>Let ground items skip into the chain</PSC_SettingsSkipLooseItems>
  <PSC_SettingsSkipLooseItemsTip>Also let an item lying on the ground go straight to the furthest storage in a route chain, instead of entering at the chain's start and moving up step by step. The chain must have an open entry: an upstream storage that accepts the item and is not set to "Pull only from sources". For such chains this lets ground items past "Pull only from sources". Only available while "Deliver straight to the end of a route chain" is on. Off by default.</PSC_SettingsSkipLooseItemsTip>
  <PSC_SettingsFineOrderHeader>Fine order</PSC_SettingsFineOrderHeader>
  <PSC_FineOrderLegend>Level {0} = highest, {1} = lowest. Letters break ties within a level: none &gt; a &gt; b &gt; c.</PSC_FineOrderLegend>
  <PSC_SettingsPriorityNumbering>Use 1–10 priority levels</PSC_SettingsPriorityNumbering>
  <PSC_SettingsPriorityNumberingTip>Split each of the five vanilla priority bands into two levels: 1 (highest) to 10 (lowest). Existing storage lands on 1, 3, 5, 7 and 10. Turn this off to collapse back to the five bands — your letters still apply, but any ordering that relied on a level difference within one band stops working until you turn numbering back on.</PSC_SettingsPriorityNumberingTip>
  <PSC_SettingsReverseOrder>Reverse 1–10 numbering</PSC_SettingsReverseOrder>
  <PSC_SettingsReverseOrderTip>Show the highest priority as 10 instead of 1. Changes only the displayed numbers, not how storage is ordered.</PSC_SettingsReverseOrderTip>
  <PSC_SettingsHaulingHeader>Hauling</PSC_SettingsHaulingHeader>
  <PSC_SettingsReservedFill>Reserve space for in-flight hauls</PSC_SettingsReservedFill>
  <PSC_SettingsReservedFillTip>Counts items already on their way into a storage toward its maximum, so several haulers won't overshoot the limit at once. Has no effect on storages without a maximum. On by default.</PSC_SettingsReservedFillTip>
  <PSC_SettingsPerTileLimits>Enable per-cell stockpile limits</PSC_SettingsPerTileLimits>
  <PSC_SettingsPerTileLimitsTip>Adds a "Max per cell" field to floor stockpiles so haulers spread items thin across many cells instead of one dense stack. Niche: mainly for spreading flammables like wood or chemfuel. Floor stockpiles only. Off by default.</PSC_SettingsPerTileLimitsTip>
  <PSC_SettingsOverlayHeader>Feeder overlay</PSC_SettingsOverlayHeader>
  <PSC_SettingsPortSpreading>Spread route endpoints</PSC_SettingsPortSpreading>
  <PSC_SettingsPortSpreadingTip>Fan route lines out along each storage's edge instead of running them all through its centre, so a tangle of routes stays readable. Off by default; turn on if your routes overlap and become hard to read.</PSC_SettingsPortSpreadingTip>
  <PSC_SettingsFocusDim>Dim unrelated routes</PSC_SettingsFocusDim>
  <PSC_SettingsFocusDimTip>When the overlay shows every route, fade out the ones that don't touch the storage under your cursor (or the selected one), so its routes stand out. On by default.</PSC_SettingsFocusDimTip>
  <PSC_SettingsFlowDots>Animated flow dots</PSC_SettingsFlowDots>
  <PSC_SettingsFlowDotsTip>While you hover or select a storage, show dots flowing along its working routes (over a faint direction arrow). Only its routes animate, and only ones that actually move items. On by default.</PSC_SettingsFlowDotsTip>
  <PSC_SettingsDotsOnly>Flowing dots, no arrows</PSC_SettingsDotsOnly>
  <PSC_SettingsDotsOnlyTip>Replace the direction arrows with dots flowing along every working route, all the time. Direction is shown by the dots' motion instead of arrowheads. Off by default; an experimental look.</PSC_SettingsDotsOnlyTip>
  <PSC_SettingsChainHighlight>Highlight feeder chains</PSC_SettingsChainHighlight>
  <PSC_SettingsChainHighlightTip>When you select or hover a storage, light up the whole chain it belongs to: the routes it feeds, the routes that feed it, and onward. Each step further away fades a little. On by default; turn off to show only the storage's own direct routes.</PSC_SettingsChainHighlightTip>
  <PSC_SettingsDirectionColor>Colour outgoing routes amber</PSC_SettingsDirectionColor>
  <PSC_SettingsDirectionColorTip>Tint routes leaving a focused storage amber and routes arriving at it green, so you can tell incoming from outgoing at a glance. Routes that won't move items stay red either way. On by default.</PSC_SettingsDirectionColorTip>
  <PSC_SettingsHashShading>Separate crowded routes</PSC_SettingsHashShading>
  <PSC_SettingsHashShadingTip>Vary each route's shade (brightness and a touch of hue) so a bundle of overlapping lines reads as separate routes instead of one blob. Stays clearly green, amber, or red. On by default.</PSC_SettingsHashShadingTip>
  <PSC_SettingsLineWidth>Route line width: {0}</PSC_SettingsLineWidth>
  <PSC_SettingsDebugHeader>Debugging</PSC_SettingsDebugHeader>
  <PSC_SettingsDebugLogging>Verbose debug logging</PSC_SettingsDebugLogging>
  <PSC_SettingsDebugLoggingTip>Logs PSC's hauling and ordering decisions to the dev console / Player.log. For bug reports only; leave off for normal play.</PSC_SettingsDebugLoggingTip>
  <PSC_SettingsResetAll>Reset to default</PSC_SettingsResetAll>
  <PSC_SettingsResetAllTip>Restore ALL Precision Stockpile Control settings to their defaults, across every tab, not just this one.</PSC_SettingsResetAllTip>

  <!-- Fine order: priority box beside the vanilla Priority button -->
  <PSC_LevelShort>Lvl {0}</PSC_LevelShort>
  <PSC_LevelBox>Lvl {0} — {1}</PSC_LevelBox>
  <PSC_LevelTip>Priority level — {0} = highest, {1} = lowest. Each vanilla priority band splits into two levels; setting a level also sets the band.</PSC_LevelTip>
  <PSC_LevelOption>{0} — {1}</PSC_LevelOption>
  <PSC_LetterTip>Tiebreaker within the same priority. Order: none (highest) &gt; a &gt; b &gt; c … &gt; z.</PSC_LetterTip>
  <PSC_LetterNone>None (highest)</PSC_LetterNone>

  <!-- Sequential subpriority painter gizmo -->
  <PSC_PaintSubpriority>Paint subpriority</PSC_PaintSubpriority>
  <PSC_PaintSubpriorityDesc>Click or drag over other storage to give each the next letter in sequence below this one. This storage stays put, and every painted storage adopts its priority level. Stops at "z". Right-click to cancel.</PSC_PaintSubpriorityDesc>
  <PSC_PaintNext>Next: {0}</PSC_PaintNext>
  <PSC_PaintClamp>Reached the lowest letter ("z"). Set any remaining storage by hand.</PSC_PaintClamp>

  <!-- Auto-priority on new route (clamp notices) -->
  <PSC_AutoPriorityClampLow>Couldn't auto-lower the source below the destination — it's already at the lowest letter ("z"). Set the priority by hand.</PSC_AutoPriorityClampLow>
  <PSC_AutoPriorityClampHigh>Couldn't auto-raise the destination above the source — it's already at the top (no letter). Set the priority by hand.</PSC_AutoPriorityClampHigh>

  <!-- Warning when a route is created that can't carry items (destination doesn't outrank source) -->
  <PSC_RouteNotFunctional>Route created, but it won't carry items yet: a destination must outrank its source. Raise the destination's priority, lower the source's, or turn on auto-priority in settings.</PSC_RouteNotFunctional>

  <!-- Route gizmos (the source -> destination feeder relationship) -->
  <PSC_ConnectSource>Set source</PSC_ConnectSource>
  <PSC_ConnectSourceDesc>Click or drag over other storage to route items from it into this one. Items move here when this storage outranks the source. (A destination must outrank its source.)</PSC_ConnectSourceDesc>
  <PSC_ConnectDestination>Set destination</PSC_ConnectDestination>
  <PSC_ConnectDestinationDesc>Click or drag over other storage to route items from this one into it. Items move there when it outranks this storage.</PSC_ConnectDestinationDesc>
  <PSC_BreakConnection>Clear route</PSC_BreakConnection>
  <PSC_BreakConnectionDesc>Left-click or drag over a routed storage to break that one route. Right-click for bulk options: clear this storage's routes, or every route on the map.</PSC_BreakConnectionDesc>
  <PSC_OnlyFromSource>Pull only from sources</PSC_OnlyFromSource>
  <PSC_OnlyFromSourceDesc>When on, this storage accepts items only from its source storages — never ground items, and never storage it isn't routed from.</PSC_OnlyFromSourceDesc>
  <PSC_OnlyToDestinations>Push only to destinations</PSC_OnlyToDestinations>
  <PSC_OnlyToDestinationsDesc>When on, items here are hauled only to this storage's destinations — never to any other storage.</PSC_OnlyToDestinationsDesc>
  <PSC_NoSourceReason>No source set yet.</PSC_NoSourceReason>
  <PSC_NoDestinationReason>No destination set yet.</PSC_NoDestinationReason>
  <PSC_ClearConnectionsThisStockpile>Clear this storage's routes</PSC_ClearConnectionsThisStockpile>
  <PSC_ClearConnectionsConfirm>Clear all routes on this map</PSC_ClearConnectionsConfirm>
  <PSC_ClearConnectionsConfirmDialog>Remove every route on this map? This cannot be undone.</PSC_ClearConnectionsConfirmDialog>

  <!-- Scoped paste: right-click the vanilla Paste button to paste only some settings. Left-click
       still pastes everything (including priorities). -->
  <PSC_PasteScopedDesc>Paste storage settings. Right-click for scoped paste options: items only, items and routes, or everything but priorities.</PSC_PasteScopedDesc>
  <PSC_PasteItemsLimits>Paste items &amp; limits</PSC_PasteItemsLimits>
  <PSC_PasteItemsLimitsTip>Pastes only which items are allowed or disallowed and their per-item limits. Leaves routes, priorities, and everything else untouched.</PSC_PasteItemsLimitsTip>
  <PSC_PasteItemsLimitsRoutes>Paste items, limits &amp; routes</PSC_PasteItemsLimitsRoutes>
  <PSC_PasteItemsLimitsRoutesTip>Also pastes feeder routes and the pull-only / push-only flags. Leaves priorities and other settings untouched.</PSC_PasteItemsLimitsRoutesTip>
  <PSC_PasteAllButPriorities>Paste everything but priorities</PSC_PasteAllButPriorities>
  <PSC_PasteAllButPrioritiesTip>Pastes items, limits, routes, batch settings, storage mode, and alarms — everything except the priority band and fine-order level.</PSC_PasteAllButPrioritiesTip>
  <PSC_PasteEverything>Paste everything</PSC_PasteEverything>
  <PSC_PasteEverythingTip>Pastes every setting, including priorities. Same as left-clicking Paste.</PSC_PasteEverythingTip>

  <!-- On-map storage overlay (bottom-right play-settings toggle + per-storage info panels) -->
  <PSC_OverlayToggle>Storage overlay</PSC_OverlayToggle>
  <PSC_OverlayToggleTip>Show storage priority panels and all feeder routes on the map. Panels appear when you zoom in.</PSC_OverlayToggleTip>
  <PSC_OverlayLimits>Item limits set</PSC_OverlayLimits>

  <!-- Storage mode gizmo (M5.2, Flickable-style: normal / frozen / fill only / drain only) -->
  <PSC_StorageModeDesc>{0}\n\nClick to set how this storage takes items in and lets them out.</PSC_StorageModeDesc>
  <PSC_Mode_Normal>Normal</PSC_Mode_Normal>
  <PSC_Mode_NormalDesc>Items are hauled in and out normally.</PSC_Mode_NormalDesc>
  <PSC_Mode_Off>Frozen</PSC_Mode_Off>
  <PSC_Mode_OffDesc>Items this storage accepts are frozen in place: nothing is hauled in, and what's here can't be hauled out or used for cooking, crafting, building, and so on. Unforbidding them by hand does nothing; change the mode to release them. Items it would not accept (a disallowed type, or amounts over a per-item maximum) are not frozen and can still be hauled away. (Pawns in a mental break can still take items.)</PSC_Mode_OffDesc>
  <PSC_Mode_AcceptOnly>Fill only</PSC_Mode_AcceptOnly>
  <PSC_Mode_AcceptOnlyDesc>Items are hauled in normally but frozen once here: they can't leave or be used, so while it fills, cooks, doctors and bills won't draw from it (a fill-only food or ingredient pile won't feed anyone). Switch the mode to release what's here. Good for a pile that fills but never drains. Items the storage would not accept (a disallowed type, or amounts over a per-item maximum) are not frozen, so disallowed leftovers and any excess over the cap can still be hauled out.</PSC_Mode_AcceptOnlyDesc>
  <PSC_Mode_RetrieveOnly>Drain only</PSC_Mode_RetrieveOnly>
  <PSC_Mode_RetrieveOnlyDesc>No new items come in, but pawns can freely take and use what's already here. Good for emptying a storage area.</PSC_Mode_RetrieveOnlyDesc>

  <!-- Storage tab button -->
  <PSC_ButtonLabel>Stockpile Control</PSC_ButtonLabel>
  <PSC_ButtonTip>Open Precision Stockpile Control for this storage.</PSC_ButtonTip>

  <!-- Control window -->
  <PSC_WindowTitle>Precision Stockpile Control</PSC_WindowTitle>
  <PSC_Mode>Count by</PSC_Mode>
  <PSC_ModeItems>items</PSC_ModeItems>
  <PSC_ModeStacks>stacks</PSC_ModeStacks>
  <PSC_Upper>Maximum</PSC_Upper>
  <PSC_UpperShort>Max</PSC_UpperShort>
  <PSC_Lower>Refill at</PSC_Lower>
  <PSC_LowerShort>Refill</PSC_LowerShort>
  <PSC_Always>always</PSC_Always>
  <PSC_Maximum>maximum</PSC_Maximum>
  <PSC_MaxHelp>Pawns won't haul in past this count.</PSC_MaxHelp>
  <PSC_RefillHelp>Pawns ignore this storage until its count drops to here, then refill up to Maximum. Stops constant topping-up.</PSC_RefillHelp>
  <PSC_CountByTip>Count limits by individual items, or by full stacks (one stack = this item's max stack size).</PSC_CountByTip>
  <PSC_BatchFill>Batch fill</PSC_BatchFill>
  <PSC_BatchFillTip>Minimum items per haul-in trip. Pawns wait for this many to pile up at the source before fetching. 0 = no minimum.</PSC_BatchFillTip>
  <PSC_BatchEmpty>Batch empty</PSC_BatchEmpty>
  <PSC_BatchEmptyTip>Minimum items per haul-out trip. Pawns leave fewer than this in place until more piles up, so a small leftover that never grows stays put. It can still be eaten or used, but a non-consumable like steel just waits. 0 = no minimum.</PSC_BatchEmptyTip>
  <PSC_PerTileLimit>Max per cell</PSC_PerTileLimit>
  <PSC_PerTileLimitTip>Limits how many items can pile onto a single floor-stockpile cell. Set to 0 to disable. Useful for spreading flammables like wood or chemfuel thin across many cells. Floor stockpiles only.</PSC_PerTileLimitTip>
  <PSC_Preview>Will set: {0}</PSC_Preview>
  <PSC_SliderHintGlobal>Leave an end blank for: always refill / fill to maximum.</PSC_SliderHintGlobal>
  <PSC_SliderHintItem>Leave an end blank for: always refill / fill to maximum. Ticks mark stacks of {0}.</PSC_SliderHintItem>
  <PSC_SliderHintMixedStacks>Leave an end blank for: always refill / fill to maximum. "Items" is off: this selection has mixed stack sizes.</PSC_SliderHintMixedStacks>
  <PSC_ItemsModeMixedStacksTip>Can't count by items here — the selection mixes different stack sizes. Count by stacks instead.</PSC_ItemsModeMixedStacksTip>
  <PSC_SoftCapNote>Pawns respect each maximum when hauling. Items spawned straight into storage (for example a workbench standing in the zone) can still exceed it.</PSC_SoftCapNote>
  <PSC_ApplyToSearch>Apply to search</PSC_ApplyToSearch>
  <PSC_RemoveFromSearch>Clear search limits</PSC_RemoveFromSearch>
  <PSC_ApplyToAll>Apply to all allowed</PSC_ApplyToAll>
  <PSC_RemoveFromAll>Clear all limits</PSC_RemoveFromAll>
  <PSC_ApplyToSearchHint>These limits apply to every item matching the storage tab's search.</PSC_ApplyToSearchHint>
  <PSC_ApplyToAllHint>No search active — these limits apply to every item this storage allows. Type in the storage tab's search box to target specific items.</PSC_ApplyToAllHint>

  <!-- One-way migration from other stockpile-limit mods -->
  <PSC_MigrationLetterLabel>Stockpile limits imported</PSC_MigrationLetterLabel>
  <PSC_MigrationImportedLine>Imported limits from {0} for {1} storage area(s).</PSC_MigrationImportedLine>
  <PSC_MigrationCaveat>Some values were approximated — open a storage's Stockpile Control panel to review or adjust them. Settings PSC can't express (per-stack-size or percentage-only) were skipped.</PSC_MigrationCaveat>
  <PSC_MigrationFailed>{0} storage area(s) couldn't be imported and stay unlimited.</PSC_MigrationFailed>
  <PSC_MigrationModSatisfiedStorage>Satisfied Storage</PSC_MigrationModSatisfiedStorage>
  <PSC_MigrationModVarietyMatters>Variety Matters Stockpile</PSC_MigrationModVarietyMatters>
  <PSC_MigrationModStackGap>Stack Gap</PSC_MigrationModStackGap>

  <!-- Per-item / category limit submenu (right-click a filter row or category) -->
  <PSC_Apply>Apply</PSC_Apply>
  <PSC_Cancel>Cancel</PSC_Cancel>
  <PSC_AllowClear>✓ Allow, no limit</PSC_AllowClear>
  <PSC_DisallowClear>✗ Disallow</PSC_DisallowClear>

  <!-- Stockpile alarm (gizmo + dialog): alert when a storage gets too full or too empty -->
  <PSC_Alarm_GizmoLabel>Stockpile alarm</PSC_Alarm_GizmoLabel>
  <PSC_Alarm_GizmoDesc>Get an alert when this storage gets too full or too empty.\n\nLeft-click to set it up. Right-click to disarm this storage, or every alarm on the map.</PSC_Alarm_GizmoDesc>
  <PSC_Alarm_FallbackLabel>Stockpile</PSC_Alarm_FallbackLabel>
  <PSC_Alarm_HighLabel>Alert when full is at or above</PSC_Alarm_HighLabel>
  <PSC_Alarm_LowLabel>Alert when full is at or below</PSC_Alarm_LowLabel>
  <PSC_Alarm_OverlapWarning>The high threshold should be above the low threshold.</PSC_Alarm_OverlapWarning>
  <PSC_Alarm_Sustain>Only alert if it lasts</PSC_Alarm_Sustain>
  <PSC_Alarm_Hours>hours</PSC_Alarm_Hours>
  <PSC_Alarm_SustainTip>How long the storage must stay over/under the threshold before alerting, so brief spikes are ignored. Leave at 0 to alert right away.</PSC_Alarm_SustainTip>
  <PSC_Alarm_Repeat>Repeat</PSC_Alarm_Repeat>
  <PSC_Alarm_Repeat_OneShot>Once, then cancel</PSC_Alarm_Repeat_OneShot>
  <PSC_Alarm_Repeat_Daily>Once per day</PSC_Alarm_Repeat_Daily>
  <PSC_Alarm_Repeat_Quadrum>Once per quadrum</PSC_Alarm_Repeat_Quadrum>
  <PSC_Alarm_Notify>Notify with</PSC_Alarm_Notify>
  <PSC_Alarm_Notify_Message>Message</PSC_Alarm_Notify_Message>
  <PSC_Alarm_Notify_Letter>Letter</PSC_Alarm_Notify_Letter>
  <PSC_Alarm_CustomMessage>Custom message</PSC_Alarm_CustomMessage>
  <PSC_Alarm_CustomHint>Leave blank to use the default, which names the storage and its fill %.</PSC_Alarm_CustomHint>
  <PSC_Alarm_CurrentFullness>Currently {0}% full</PSC_Alarm_CurrentFullness>
  <PSC_Alarm_CurrentFullnessUnknown>No storage cells</PSC_Alarm_CurrentFullnessUnknown>
  <PSC_Alarm_HighMsg>{0} is {1}% full.</PSC_Alarm_HighMsg>
  <PSC_Alarm_LowMsg>{0} is low — only {1}% full.</PSC_Alarm_LowMsg>
  <PSC_Alarm_LetterTitle>Stockpile alarm: {0}</PSC_Alarm_LetterTitle>
  <PSC_Alarm_ArmHigh>Arm high alarm (≥ {0}% full)</PSC_Alarm_ArmHigh>
  <PSC_Alarm_ArmLow>Arm low alarm (≤ {0}% full)</PSC_Alarm_ArmLow>
  <PSC_Alarm_DisarmThis>Disarm alarm (this storage)</PSC_Alarm_DisarmThis>
  <PSC_Alarm_DisarmAll>Disarm all alarms (this map)</PSC_Alarm_DisarmAll>
  <PSC_Alarm_DisarmAllConfirm>Disarm every stockpile alarm on this map? This cannot be undone.</PSC_Alarm_DisarmAllConfirm>

  <!-- Storage-tab quick-toggle strip (right of the Stockpile Control button) -->
  <PSC_Toggle_StateOn>On</PSC_Toggle_StateOn>
  <PSC_Toggle_StateOff>Off</PSC_Toggle_StateOff>
  <PSC_Toggle_BatchValue>min {0} per trip</PSC_Toggle_BatchValue>
  <PSC_Toggle_BatchInHint>Left-click turns batch-fill on or off (default {0} items). Right-click opens Stockpile Control to set the exact amount.</PSC_Toggle_BatchInHint>
  <PSC_Toggle_BatchOutHint>Left-click turns batch-empty on or off (default {0} items). Right-click opens Stockpile Control to set the exact amount.</PSC_Toggle_BatchOutHint>
  <PSC_Toggle_AlarmHint>Left-click arms a high-fill alarm (≥ {0}% full) or disarms this storage's alarm. Right-click opens the alarm settings.</PSC_Toggle_AlarmHint>

</LanguageData>
